14dayz.com 2010-12-31

# 14Dayz.com - Time Tracking Made Simple

## Privacy policy

* * *

##### Introduction

**Brains4All is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to our website, as well as our account holders and clients. In general Brains4All treats your contact information as private and confidential. Brains4All will not give, sell, rent, exchange or otherwise provide your information with anyone else without your prior consent (except when compelled by law — see below).**

##### Website Policy

Brains4All servers may record the IP address of the computer you are using; the browser software you use and your operating system; the date and time you access our site; and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our site.

We use this information to measure the number of visitors to different sections of the site, to diagnose and correct system errors, and to improve the site. We do not connect this information to your name or identity, and we periodically delete this information from the server.

Information that is not provided with the express intent of subscription, ordering, or general use of the 14Dayz application is not saved and will not be captured for use in other communications. See below for details on how we treat information provided in subscription and ordering contexts.

We make limited use of "cookies" on this site. These cookies are only accessible by, [14Dayz.com](http://14dayz.com/) and are typically deleted as soon as possible.

##### Mailing List Policies

If you choose to subscribe to any of these lists, we may ask for personal information, such as your name, zip code, and email address. This information is used strictly to manage our lists and will be used exclusively for the purpose of sending you email from Brains4All. You will not be contacted in any other way, nor will your information be offered to a third-party. We do not sell, rent or share our mailing lists.

You can unsubscribe from any of our lists at any time. In the event you wish to update or delete an email address in our possession at any time for any reason, please contact [support@14dayz.com](mailto:support@14dayz.com) to make those changes.

Lists maintained by Brains4All for repeated mailings are exclusively "opt-in" lists. We do not purchase information from third-party sources or gather personal data from the web for inclusion in our ongoing E-mail lists.

##### Subscription and Orders

Brains4All will never share or use personal information provided in the course of becoming a paid or free plan subscriber for any reason other than to manage your subscription or license.

A minimum amount of information will be exchanged with our payment providers necessary to fulfill your order or subscription. 

Information provided to us in the course of placing an order may be retained for use in future communications. This information will not be sold, rented, shared or otherwise provided to anyone else without your prior consent (to procure payment or except when compelled by law — see below).

##### Compelled Disclosure

If we are required by law to disclose any information that you have provided us, we will attempt to give you notice (unless we are prohibited) that a request for your information has been made, in order to give you an opportunity to object. We will attempt to provide this notice by email, if you have given us an email address or by postal mail if you have entered a postal address. If you do not challenge the disclosure request, we may be legally required to turn over your information. 

For any other information about our privacy policy, please contact [privacy@14dayz.com](mailto:privacy@14dayz.com)
